<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Works on Fairese</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/work/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Works on Fairese</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 19:10:07 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/work/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>n8n Automations</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/n8n-automations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 19:10:07 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/n8n-automations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;n8n-automation-work&#34;&gt;n8n Automation Work&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;n8n is a powerful workflow automation tool that connects APIs, databases, and services without heavy custom code. It can be used to automate repetitive tasks, integrate disparate systems, and build data flows that run on a schedule or in real time.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Work in this area can include designing and implementing workflows for data processing, API integration, notification systems, and business process automation — either self-hosted or in the cloud — with a focus on maintainable, well-documented automations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Clients</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/work/clients/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 22:37:20 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/work/clients/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Before founding Fairese LLC, Andy Ibanez collaborated with a range of clients and companies across various industries. This page highlights a curated selection of those collaborations, though it is not a complete list. Some projects are omitted due to NDAs or other confidentiality agreements.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;trax-aero&#34;&gt;TRAX Aero&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/images/pages/trax-logo.png&#34; alt=&#34;TRAX Logo&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.trax.aero&#34;&gt;TRAX&lt;/a&gt; develops software for the airplane maintenance industry. Trax started as a small mom-and-pop shop back in 1997 and it has grown to become one of the most important companies in the industry. Serving over 225 clients, it delivers mission-critical solutions to airlines and maintenance organizations worldwide. TRAX offers its &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.trax.aero/products/emobility/&#34;&gt;eMobility&lt;/a&gt; suite of apps, all of which serve a different purpose for personnel in the aircraft maintenance industry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
